m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8
m 50 0 l 179 0 b 208 0 229 21 229 50 l 229 179 b 229 208 208 228 179 228 l 50 228 b 21 228 0 208 0 179 l 0 50 b 0 21 21 0 50 0
m 0 0 b 1 -1 2 -2 4 -1 b 7 1 3 2 5 5 b 6 7 8 7 9 5 l 15 -6 b 18 -7 20 -6 20 -3 b 19 -1 17 2 17 4 b 16 7 20 7 21 6 b 22 4 23 2 25 -1 b 27 -2 29 -1 29 1 b 29 2 28 3 29 5 b 30 7 32 7 33 6 b 34 5 34 4 35 3 b 37 2 39 3 39 5 b 39 6 38 8 37 9 b 34 13 29 13 25 9 b 22 13 17 13 13 9 b 10 13 3 13 0 8
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
翻译     随时放空赛太公   油腻希
校对     光速切屏赛哥
m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
后期      灰灰是菇凉      时间轴    加森
总监     新浪微博@赛太公
♪ 世上没人比我强壮 ♪
♪ Nobody else is stronger than I am ♪
♪ 昨天我移了一座山 ♪
♪ Yesterday I moved a mountain ♪
♪ 我相信我能当你的英雄 ♪
♪ I bet I could be your hero ♪
♪ 我是个了不起的小家伙 ♪
♪ I am a mighty little man ♪
少
年
谢尔顿
《少年谢尔顿》前情提要
Previously on Young Sheldon...
什么情况
What the hell's going on?
妈妈觉得我疯了
Mom thinks that I'm crazy.
我们不是说好不提这种字眼吗
I thought we weren't supposed to say stuff like that.
宝贝  有件事我得告诉你
Baby, there's something I need to tell you.
斯特吉斯博士
Dr. Sturgis
不是住进了你想的那种医院
is not in the kind of hospital you think he is.
那他是在哪种医院
What kind of hospital is he in?
精神病院
The psychiatric kind.
你觉得因为我和他都有天赋
And you think since he and I are both gifted,
我以后也会变成他那样吗
I'm going to end up like him?
宝贝
Oh, baby.
看见没  一点沟通就能有巨大的效果
See how valuable a little communication can be?
这事你屁功劳都没有
You do not take credit for this.
你永远不会知道科学灵感何时会来临
You never know where scientific inspiration will strike.
牛顿是坐在苹果树下时
For Newton, it was under an apple tree.
阿基米德是坐在浴缸里时
For Archimedes, it was sitting in a bathtub.
而我呢  在那一天
For me, on this particular day,
感觉会在"流汗的人们吃着肉"时来灵感
it had a "Sweaty people eating meat" kind of vibe.
谢尔顿  你一定要在这里搞这些吗
Sheldon, do you really have to do that here?
如果店里的人不想我解开统一场论
If the management didn't want me to solve unified field theory,
那他们为什么要给我蜡笔呢
why would they give me a crayon?
我就跟你说车窗开个缝  把他留车上吧
I told you to crack a window and leave him in the car.
我灵光一闪
It occurred to me
如果麦克斯韦方程组中加入一个磁单极子
that Maxwell's equations would achieve full symmetry
就能达到完全对称
by adding a magnetic monopole.
我画了一只瓢虫
I drew a ladybug.
好啦好啦
All right, y'all.
我可以把菜放下吗
Oh... ‭Is it okay to set this down?
我现在这里正忙着  你能等会再上菜吗
I'm a little busy. Could you come back later?
谢尔顿  我很饿了
Sheldon, I'm hungry.
我们坐过去隔壁桌吧
Let's just sit over there.
不行  我们一家得坐同一桌一起用餐
No. We're gonna eat together as a family.
这样就不是电力  而是电磁力
Instead of electricity, we'll have magnetricity.
我快举不动了
It's getting heavy.
我们就坐隔壁  有事就叫我们
We'll be right over here if you need us.
过去吧
Let's go.
再见啦  小瓢虫
Bye, ladybug.
宝贝  你必须得吃点东西
Baby, you need to eat something.
感觉我可以改变
But it looks like I can change the definitions
电力与电磁场的定义
of electric and magnetic fields
这样磁荷这个变量就不会为0
and rotate the magnetic charge away mathematically to zero.
或许吃一点炸秋葵会有帮助
Maybe some fried okra would help.
理查德·费曼发明量子电动力学时
Richard Feynman didn't develop quantum electrodynamics
靠的可不是吃炸秋葵
by filling up on fried okra.
那可能是因为他妈妈爱他的程度
Well, maybe that's because his mama didn't love him
没有我爱你那么深啊
as much as I love you.
理查德·费曼是犹太人
Richard Feynman was Jewish.
他的妈妈才不可能给他吃炸秋葵[黑人菜]
His mother didn't give him fried okra.
我是漏了哪里呢
Ugh. What am I missing?
你再吵醒我一次
Wake me up one more time,
我就往你手套里打喷嚏
and I will sneeze in your mittens.
打一个带鼻涕的大喷嚏进去
A big, wet, snotty one.
小宝贝  你在干嘛呢
Baby, what are you doing?
做事
Working.
你是一整晚没睡待在这里吗
Have you been out here all night?
没有啊  怎么这么问  现在几点了
No. Why, what time is it?
7点30
7:30.
那我是待了一晚
Oh. Then yes.
我了个...
Son of a...
老爸  你在忙吗
Dad, you busy?
我表情看起来像在忙吗
Do I look like I'm busy?
你在水槽底下  我看不见你表情啊
I can't see what you look like. You're under the sink.
找我什么事
What do you want?
你可以教我怎么投球吗
Would you teach me how to throw a baseball?
怎么突然想学了
What's bringing this on?
我也不知道  就感觉挺好玩
I don't know, just seems fun.
行啊  有何不可
Sure, why not?
太好了  我去拿手套
Great, I'll get the gloves.
不是现在
Not now!
有什么新鲜事啊
So, what's new?
我有点担心谢尔顿
I'm worried about Sheldon.
我说了是"新鲜事"
I said "new."
他都不睡觉  也不吃饭
He's not sleeping, he's not eating.
我们昨晚出门吃烧烤
We went out for barbecue last night,
他一口都没吃
and he didn't touch a thing.
他还开始咬指甲了
He also started biting his nails.
我从没看过他有这习惯
I've never seen him do that before.
他心里有什么烦恼吗
Is he worried about something?
他一心想着一个科学的问题
He's fixated on some science problem.
我确定他会解开的
Well, I'm sure he'll solve it
然后一切就会变回原来那样
and then everything will go back to normal.
希望如此
I hope so.
约翰最近怎么样了
What's going on with John?
一切如常
Not much.
我们就书信往来
We write letters back and forth.
那很浪漫啊
That's romantic.
他是上前线写信才浪漫啊
Romantic if he were off to war,
他进精神病院有什么浪漫的
not in a mental hospital.
他也是在跟心魔打仗啊
Well, he's at war with his inner demons.
-你是右撇子吧  -你不知道吗
- You're right-handed, yeah? - You don't know?
行啊  聪明鬼  那我是左撇子还右撇子
Okay, smartass, which one am I?
我是右撇子
I'm right-handed.
那把手套戴上你的左手
Put this on your left hand.
你以前投过球吗
You ever thrown a ball before?
只用石头丢过谢尔顿
Just rocks at Sheldon.
有丢中吗
Did you hit him?
每次都中了
Every time.
很好  那我们算有些基础
So, we got something to work with.
好  根据我新学到的  你是右撇子
All right, since you're right-handed, which I now know,
你要把你的右手臂举起
you're gonna bring your arm up
然后顺着这动作丢出去
and follow through like this.
好
Okay.
很棒  你可能很有天赋
Nice. You might be a natural.
我不意外  这可是我平常画画上色的那只手
I'm not surprised. This is the arm I color with.
我都没意识到我在啃手指
I wasn't even aware I was chewing them.
宝贝  我觉得这个数学题
Baby, I think this math problem
你为了解开  把自己逼过头了
you're working on is stressing you out.
很有可能  毕竟爱因斯坦辛苦了30年
It makes sense. Einstein struggled with it for 30 years
最后都还是没有解开
and never found a solution.
或许你先别想  放一放  之后灵感就来了呢
Maybe if you stop thinking about it, it'll just come to you.
-不  我不能停下  -谢尔顿
- No. I can't stop. ‭- Sheldon.
如果我停下  就会失去动力
If I stop, I'll lose momentum.
然后就永远解不开  我就会是个失败者
I'll never solve it. I'll be a failure.
我的人生就会比咸鱼还不如
My life will be worthless.
好了够了  你必须停止搞科学一阵子
Okay, that's it. You're taking a break from science.
给我一个应该这么做的好理由
Give me one good reason why I would do that.
斯特吉斯博士现在沦落到哪了
Where is Dr. Sturgis right now?
这是个好理由
That's a good reason.
你要记得  眼睛盯着
All right, remember, you need to look
你想要球飞过去的落点
right where you want the ball to go.
不然我还能看哪里
Where else would I look?
光是刚才五分钟
Well, in the last five minutes,
我就看到你看了蝴蝶
I saw you watch a butterfly,
一只松鼠  还有卖冰激凌的卡车
a squirrel and the ice cream truck.
你自己也看了冰激凌卡车啊
You looked at the ice cream truck, too.
哪个队伍的球帽上有个大红"T"字
Which team has a big red "T" on their hat?
德州游骑兵队
Texas Rangers.
-是受我们喜爱的队伍吗  -是啊
- Is that a team we like? - Uh, yeah.
这里大多数的人都支持他们
Yeah, that's who most people around here root for.
那如果要聊这队  我可以说些什么呢
Okay. And what's something I could say about the Rangers?
说出来会让人惊叹的
You know, to sound cool.
-这是跟小男生有关吗  -不是
- Is this about a boy? - ‭No.
抱歉  是我误会了
All right, sorry.
如果想聊  你可以说"虽然诺兰·莱恩老了
If you want, you could say, "Even though Nolan Ryan is old,
但游骑兵队招揽他来十分明智"
the Rangers were still smart to get him."
真有这回事吗
That's a real thing?
这是真的
That's a real thing.
诺兰·莱恩几岁了
How old is Nolan Ryan?
美国职棒大联盟史上第一的三振王
1947年出生  1993年在游骑兵队退休
我这年纪
My age.
恶心
Ew.
我太习惯整天想着科学了
I'm so used to thinking about science,
我不知道该怎么让自己停下
I'm not sure how to make myself stop.
一旦我开始想着
As soon as I think about
我要不想科学  我就又重新开始想了
not thinking about it, I'm thinking about it.
那你为什么不想点别的呢
Well, why don't you just think about something else?
-比如呢  -不知道啊
- Like what? ‭- I don't know.
看漫画呢
Read a comic book?
你觉得咬了彼得·帕克的蜘蛛
How do you think the spider that bit Peter Parker
是怎么有放射性的  是科学
got radioactive? Science.
你觉得布鲁斯·班纳是怎么受到伽马射线照射的
How do you think Bruce Banner got exposed to gamma rays?
-是科学  -行了
- Science. - ‭All right.
当绿魔在飞...
When the Green Goblin flies...
-我说行了  -是科学
- I said all right. - ‭Science.
我知道你不会想听这个
I know you don't want to hear this,
但我发现祈祷可以给心灵带来无上平静
but I find prayer can bring incredible peace of mind.
别闹了  玛丽  我在想办法帮这孩子呢
Come on, Mary, I'm trying to help the kid.
你需要一个新爱好
You just need a new hobby.
很好  那你有什么爱好
Very well. What are yours?
抽烟  喝酒  赌博
Smoking, drinking and gambling.
但我们可以给你找到差不多有趣的事情啊
But we can find you something almost as fun.
《理查德·西蒙斯的体操演唱会》
再来一起流汗吧
Let's sweat again!
大家一起来
Come on, everybody!
跟上啊  谢尔顿
Come on, Sheldon.
一起来热血沸腾吧
Let's get that blood pumping.
谢了  不必
I'd rather not. ‭
做嘛  稍微运动一下
Do it. A little exercise will help
有助于把头伸出你的龟壳
get your head out of your butt.
手部动作做起来
Get those hands going.
回到前面
Back to the front.
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
我觉得我想死
I think I hate this.
但好歹你现在没心思想科学了吧
Well, you're not thinking about science now, am I right?
因为我在想我有多想死
I'm thinking about how miserable I am.
一起搭火车  来吧
Let's get on that train. Can we?
换回前面  来
Back to the front. Come on.
三
Three.
四  帮我一起数出来
Yes. Four. Count them out for me!
五
Five.
B14
B-14.
有几张独立的宾果卡
B  I  G  O列
从15中选5
第N列
从15中选4
你还有什么别的
What else you got?
你确定别人的手指没进过这里面吗
Are you positive other people's fingers haven't been in this?
我特别帮你弄了一颗新球
I made sure to get you a new one.
-感觉不新啊  -是新球
- It doesn't look new. - It's new.
出手吧
Let her rip.
我还是在想着科学
I'm still thinking about science.
没关系
That's okay.
瞄准最前面那个球瓶
Just aim for the front pin.
感觉你今天跟米希玩得很开心啊
You and Missy looked like you were having fun today.
是啊  是挺开心
Uh, yeah, we were.
你们父女俩好好培养了感情
A little father-daughter bonding.
是的  感觉很棒
Yeah. It was nice.
你们在外面待了很久
Hmm. You guys were out there for a while.
都聊了什么呀
What were you talking about?
就是人生咯
Oh, you know, just... life.
好
Sure.
没什么问题吧
Everything okay?
一点问题都没有
Everything's fine.
没什么好担心的啦
Nothing to worry about.
你真的不打算告诉人家吗
You're really not gonna tell me?
不
No.
你好啊谢尔顿  有什么能帮你的吗
Hey there, Sheldon. What can I do for ya?
不知道你有没有关于
I'm wondering if you have any books
戒掉坏习惯的书
on stopping bad habits.
有几本  你想戒掉什么习惯
A few. What habit are you trying to stop?
-科学  -妈呀
- Science. - ‭Yowza,
不是永远戒掉啦
It's not permanent.
我只是想放下一段时间
I'm just looking to take a break.
这话我以前听过
I've heard that one before.
你放下过什么
What did you take a break from?
幸福
Happiness.
好吧
Okay.
我尝试了几种不同的活动
I've tried a few different activities,
但不管我做什么  最终都把我引回科学
but whatever I do just leads me back to science.
我们来想想看  什么是跟科学截然相反的
Well, let's think about it. What's the opposite of science?
科学基于事实
Science is based in facts,
事实的对立面就是虚构作品
and the opposite of facts is fiction.
奇幻小说怎么样
How about fantasy?
有魔法和龙
Magic and dragons.
图书馆里有一整区都是这个分类
We have a whole section here.
听上去智商就要破底了
Ooh, that sounds intellectually bankrupt.
我愿意试一试
I'll give it a shot.
好消息
Good news.
我找到方法暂时放下科学了
I found a way to take a break from science.
太好了  什么方式
That's great. What is it?
叫《指环王[主]》的长篇奇幻小说
A fantasy book series called The Lord of the Rings.
至少书名里含有"主"
Well, it's got "The Lord" in it.
很了不起了
That's something.
刚才这一投还带了旋啊
That one had some zip on it.
带旋是好事吧
Zip's a good thing, right?
是的
Yes.
所以看起来我像懂行的吗
So it looks like I know what I'm doing?
跟职业球手没两样
Just like a pro.
但是淑女职业球手
But like a lady pro?
当然  非常淑女
Oh, yes. Very much.
还有什么游骑兵队的好话是我能说的
Is there anything else good I could say about the Rangers?
我想想啊
Uh, let's see.
告诉有兴趣的人
Tell whoever's interested
绝对没人能撼动诺兰·莱恩的三振出局纪录
that no one's ever gonna touch Nolan Ryan's strikeout record.
因为他经常被三振出局
'Cause he strikes out all the time.
不是的
No.
因为他经常投出好球  让对手三振出局
Because he throws ‭strikeouts all the time.
差别很大
Oh. Big difference.
晚饭好了
Dinner's ready.
再五分钟行吗
Five more minutes?
她想跟亲亲老爸再玩五分钟嘛
She wants five more minutes with her ole dad.
他们在外面干什么
What are they doing out there?
联络感情  那很棒  谢尔顿  书看得怎么样
They're bonding. It's great. Sheldon, how's your book?
话题转得真硬
Nice pivot.
非常棒  有个叫咕噜的人物
Excellent. There's a character named Gollum
被力量之戒吞蚀了心智
who was corrupted by the Ring of Power.
现在他光着身子到处乱跑  还喜欢一口咬掉鱼头
Now he runs around naked and bites the heads off fish.
那叫寿司
That's called sushi.
不过说真的  我宁死也不吃那玩意
Which, by the way, I will die before I eat.
说到死  你死了之后
Speaking of dying, when you do,
你的车能给我吗
can I have your car?
这不可能啊
This can't be right.
又怎么了
What now?
甘道夫在跃马旅店
In the letter that Gandalf leaves for Frodo
留给佛罗多的信上说  那天是年中日[6月22日]
at The Prancing Pony, he says that it's Mid-year's Day,
夏尔纪年1418年
Shire year 1418.
然而在附录二里  写着甘道夫于6月29日
However, in Appendix B, it says that Gandalf met Radagast
遇到褐袍瑞达加斯特  那是不可能的  因为...
on June 29, which is impossible because...
喂
Hey!
下次丢的就是老娘的鞋子
Next time, it's my shoe.
我还会带上旋
And I will put zip on it.
"住在镇上的男人个子很高"
"The man who lived in the town was tall."
这句话里哪个词是关系代词
Which word is the relative pronoun?
谢尔顿
Sheldon.
你读过《指环王》吗
Have you read The Lord of the Rings?
读过
Um, I have,
但我们现在不是在讨论这个
but that's not what we're really doing right now.
关系代词是"who"
The relative pronoun is "who."
你有没发现在《护戒使者》里
Now, did you notice that in Fellowship,
埃尔隆德说巴拉多的地基
Elrond says that the foundations of Barad-dur
由至尊魔戒所建成
were made with the One Ring?
就当做是吧
Let's say sure.
然而在附录二《纪年传说》中  显然
However, in Appendix B, "The Tale of Years," It's clear that
魔王索伦于第二纪元1000年开始建造巴拉多
Sauron began building Barad-dûr in Second Age 1000,
那比铸造魔戒还早了600年
600 years before the ring was forged.
小乔治
Georgie.
想象一下跟这奇葩一起生活
Imagine living with this.
每天一小时就够我受的了
An hour a day is enough.
时间线根本说不通啊
The timeline doesn't make sense.
山姆·詹吉的出生年份既有2963
I mean, it lists Samwise Gamgee's birth year as both
也有2980
2963 and 2980.
或许他谎报年龄了
Maybe he lied about his age.
-为什么  -我也不知道  或许
- Why? ‭- I don't know. Maybe he thinks
他认为他的颈纹让他显老
his neck makes him look older than he is.
但他才三十几岁
But he's only in his 30s.
还很年轻
That's young.
谢谢你啦
Thank you.
对霍比特人而言  人类到这岁数就是大妈了
For a hobbit. For a human, that's mommy-age.
谢你全家
Thank you.
当佛罗多和山姆骑马穿过夏尔时
When Frodo and Sam are riding through the Shire,
书里说月亮往西移动了
the book says the moon went westward,
但根据托尔金创作的历法
but according to the calendar Tolkien created,
当时不应该能看见月亮
there should have been no moon visible.
但在附录里  托尔金辩解道
But in the appendix, Tolkien covers himself
《西界红皮书》的翻译可能有误
by saying there may be mistranslations from the Red Book.
这是小说里的托尔金说的
Fictional Tolkien says that,
但我很想知道  是不是该书作者
but I can't help wondering if real Tolkien,
真正的托尔金犯了这个错
who wrote the book, made the mistake
还是这是小说版托尔金
or if it was an intentional mistake
他根据原始来源翻译出
made by the fictional Tolkien,
这些真实世界的事件时
who translated these real-world events
故意犯的错
from an original source.
妈呀
Oh, no.
别人听我说话时也是这感受吗
Is that how I sound to people?
闺女  你想玩投球吗
Hey! You want to throw the ball around?
不要  走开
No, go away.
学校里出什么事了吗
Did something happen at school?
我不想说
I don't want to talk about it.
好吧
Okay. Well...
如果你想谈  我随时都在
You change your mind, you know I'm here for you.
他喜欢别人
He likes someone else.
你说什么  宝贝
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
她连诺兰·莱恩是谁都不知道
She doesn't even know who Nolan Ryan is.
这男生听起来是个大白痴
This guy sounds like an idiot.
他才不是  他很完美
He's not. He's perfect.
好吧
All right.
想让我叫妈妈来吗
Want me to get your mom?
不要
No.
想让我去揍他一顿吗
You want me to beat this guy up?
不要
No.
我能做什么
What can I do?
真不错
Nice.
怎么投出曲球啊
How do you make it curve?
这有点难度
Well, that's a little tricky.
把两根手指压在接缝上
You... you put two fingers on the seam.
看到了吗  然后转动手腕
Right? And then you flick your wrist.
-好  -知道了吗  来  试一下
- Okay. - ‭Yeah? Here, try it.
两根...  放这里啊
Two... Oh, so there.
这就对了  放在接缝上
There you go, right on the stitch there.
两根手指放在上面
Two fingers on it.
-然后球脱手前一刻  转动手腕  -这样吗
- Then at the end, you flick your wrist. - ‭Like that?
就是这样  投一个试试
There you go. Give her a shot.
还挺厉害啊
Hey! How about that?
对吧  我就说了跟职业球手没两样
Right? Just like a pro, I'm telling you.
我们要再多练习
Well, we'll work on that, shall we?
绝对的
Definitely. ‭
不错
Nice.
遍寻答案无果后
Having found no answers,
我决定自己纠正
I took it upon myself to rectify
《指环王》中前后矛盾的时间线
the inconsistent timeline in Lord of the Rings.
J.R.R.托尔金是很聪明没错
J.R.R. Tolkien had a brilliant mind,
但老实说
but let's be honest.
他跟S.L.库珀比差远了
He was no S.L. Cooper.
你还好吧
You okay out here?
等我完成这个就会好了
I will be once I finish this.
纵使我很努力想排列出前后一致的年表
As hard as I tried to work out a consistent chronology,
我还是不断遇到障碍
I kept running into roadblocks.
我漏掉了什么
What am I missing?
我们永远都不会想明白的
We're never going to figures it out.
我们可以的  我们很聪明  我们绝顶聪明
We can, we're smarts. We're so smarts.
我们的大脑就是宝贝
Our brains is precious.
如果我们的大脑是宝贝
If our brains is precious,
那都浪费在霍比特人身上了
we're wasting it on hobbitses.
我们喜欢科学
We like sciences.
我们暂时放下科学了
We took a break from sciences.
科学快把我们逼疯了
It was making us crazy.
结果我们现在成什么样子了
And look at us now.
瞧那些恶心的霍比特人对我们做了什么
Look at what those nasty hobbitses have done to us.
不  是物理
No, it was physicses.
是物理害我们变成这样
Physicses did this to us.
是霍比特人
Hobbitses.
是物理
Physicses.
霍比特人
Hobbitses.
我警告过你的
I warned you.
妈妈  妈妈
Mom. Mom.
怎么了
‭What's wrong?
我变成咕噜和史麦戈了  在一个山洞里
I was Gollum and Smeagol and I was in a cave
跟我自己争辩物理和霍比特人
fighting with myself over physics and hobbits.
但之后我意识到  虽然物理使我崩溃沮丧
And then I realized that even though physics is frustrating,
但它不会把我变成受尽折磨
it won't turn me into a tormented creature
爱把鱼头生生咬下来的怪物
who bites the heads off fish.
说完了  晚安
Okay, good night.
我给米希当好爸爸了
I've been doing a great job with Missy.
你去给他当好妈妈
This one's on you.